# **DOMINIC EFEOGHENE ADJEH**

Lagos, Nigeria · +2348158389029 · dominicadjeh@gmail.com

### **SUMMARY**

A detail-oriented, organized and meticulous employee. Performed excellently and worked closely with several teams towards established goals. Contributed to team exercises, performed with merit and contributed my quota to the attainment of corporate vision having acquired relevant Project management and Programming knowledge.

# **EDUCATION**

#### • November 2020 - Present

B.Eng. Computer Engineering, First Class (Honors). Elizade University, Ilara Mokin Ondo State.

### • 2019

SSCE Certificate King's College, Lagos.

## **EXPERIENCE**

# **Graphics Designer**

# Gibraltar Technologies

(August 2021 – October 2021)

- Completed final touches for projects such as images sizes and font selection
  - Observed how edits were made on recorded videos obtained from event coverage
  - Conducted interviews with clients.
  - Took pictures of events to be supplied to the graphic designers.
  - Assisted the Newsletter and Magazine department in updating newsletters.

## **Fullstack Developer**

# HIIT PLC Ikeja, Lagos.

(August 2023 – November 2023)

- Completed a certification course in Frontend development (HTML CSS and JavaScript)
- Completed a certification course in Backend Development using Django Framework
- Designed an E-Commerce Web Application using HTML, CSS, JavaScript and Python(Django)

## **SKILLS**

skills: Python Programming | Sales | Microsoft Office Suite

**interests:** Product Development | Gaming | Economics

## ACHIEVEMENTS AND AWARDS

• Recognition of Brilliant Academic Performance (December 2022)

Elizade University, Ilara Mokin.

• Obtained distinctions in: Digital Systems, Computational Software, Object Oriented Programming and Design from Elizade University.

# **REFRENCES**

Available upon request.